In a far-off place,
amidst vengeance and enmity...
flourished an inseparable friendship.
Who is it?
Who?
Hey, Deva!
Forget it.
-Listen to me.
-Tell Me.
Who is it?
Deva!
-Why did you touch him?
-Deva, don't!
Oh...
I thought you were bringing a huge army.
But you got only him?
Just because you are born to my father
you won't get the right
to wear that nose ring.
You have to earn it.
Just tell me how.
Do you see that wrestler?
He is my champion.
He has not yet known what defeat is.
Any challenger here?
There is no man here?
Make him fall to the ground.
I will give back your nose ring.
How is that even possible?
How can he make him fall to the ground?
Answer me, anybody here?
Absolutely no pressure.
The nose ring will remain
with me.
If you don't have the courage, back off...
...step-brother.
Rudra, you are making a mistake.
You know me very well.
But, you don't know about him.
He will hit him so hard
that he would fly.
Before he finishes him off,
give back my nose ring.
If there is anyone, come forward.
He?
What will he do?
Tell me!
Come on!
Is there no man here?
What is he even capable of?
At least, there is one man here.
Get lost!
Hey, Deva!
I told you to get lost!
Deva!
He is going to die.
Don't!
Deva?
Deva, open your eyes!
Deva!
Did he fall to the ground?
Give it back!
Give it to me.
If you touch his nose ring again
It won't be an electric wire
in my hands.
It will be an electric pole.
Let's go!
In a far-off place
those who lose the battle
used to lose everything.
I want her.
I will go first.
-I will show you. I...
-I want her.
Hey!
If you try to touch his mother...
I will kill you all.
Go away from here!
Sir, don't stand in our way.
This is your father's order.
Nobody can
disobey him.
It should be done.
If you leave now, I will give you
my territory in return.
Varadha, think again.
I will give you Bharghat.
Bharghat is mine!
Bharghat...
Out of all our territories
this is the biggest.
That is exactly why
I gave it to him, Baba.
Bharghat is mine!
No one outside of here
should know about this.
Get lost now!
Hey, let's go.
Bharghat belongs to me!
Deva.
I am here for you.
Don't worry.
You shouldn't stay here anymore.
You must leave immediately.
In that far-off place
even those close friends
had to part ways.
Hey, make it quick.
Promise me
that you will never
come back to this place.
You should forget whatever happened here.
Promise me.
Deva!
I am ready to be the hunted
or the hunter for you.
Only for you.
Whenever you call me
I will come back to this place.
I don't know if you remember.
The story I told you when
you were a kid.
A sultan of the Persian empire
wouldn't deploy his formidable
army no matter how big the problem is.
Instead, he would go to only one man.
He, who fulfills whatever
the Sultan wished for
and destroys the Sultan's opponents.
That man was called...
I know, Baba.
Salaar!
He will come back.
My Salaar!
The sun sewed a wing
And winked his eyes with love
Has the beautiful twilight cloud come?
Have the rain cloud
poured down jasmine flowers?
You are the one
who was born in the sky
My lucky star, be my precious gold
on this earth.
Be a song, my beloved,
who touched my heart
One will hold the bow
And the other will be the arrow.
One is a roar and the other
is the turbulent sea.
Together they make deluge.
One is bravery
and the other a trident.
The new day will be a day of battle.
Now it will be a love that
where blessing merges with letters.
May it flourish a hundred years.
Please come with me.
I'll show you the stock.
Okay.
-Hello!
-Bilal!
My daughter is on her way to India.
Have you gone crazy?
-Why did you let her?
-Do you think I did?
She came there on her own.
If they come to know
anything about her...
No need for any doubt.
They have been searching
for the past seven years.
They would've known by now.
Radha Rama...
She is not a harmless soul
sitting quietly in a corner.
You have no idea
how powerful she is today.
After all, even Radha Rama's maid,
Obulamma
can decide the fate
of elections in certain constituencies.
Mother!
Speak.
We have finally found.
Not him.
We found his daughter.
Hey!
Krishnakanth had created eight fake
passports for himself and his daughter.
And one of these passports has been used
to book a ticket from the US to India.
Tomorrow at 6 o'clock in the morning...
she will land at Lal Bahadur Shastry
International Airport, Babatpur.
Apart from this, she has
two notorious henchmen.
Vedha...
Krishnakanth's daughter
is coming to India, sir.
Krishnakanth's daughter?
Hazare.
Tell me, Obulamma.
Krishnakanth's daughter
has come here.
I want her at any cost!
-Jessy!
-Sir?
I have a lot
of election works here.
Leave for Babatpur immediately.
Okay, sir.
For what you did to them seven years ago,
they will pay back
using your daughter.
Please do something, Bilal.
But what can I do?
Only you know his whereabouts.
So?
You remember the promise, Bilal?
Brother, show us the goods.
Get out! All of you, out!
The time has come to fulfill your promise.
I know you won't come,
no matter what I say.
I am sending someone to you.
Whatever you decide, do it.
Three cars have been arranged...
...at the airport parking.
In the street next to the airport...
There are two cars and a tempo traveler.
Come on!
What is going on?
- Hey...
-Come.
-Who are you?
Hey! No, no... No!
Come on, quick!
Go, go!
Hey, go! Chase them!
Hey, hey!
What the hell is happening?
Why are they attacking me?
There must be some sort of a mistake.
D-Did you see them, they...
They just shot that guy in the middle
of the road in broad daylight...
Speak.
Listen to me carefully, Aadhya.
-Dad! Dad...
-The guy who is with you.
Do as he says.
I will get you out of there
very soon.
Don't call me under any circumstances.
No... Dad...
Listen to me, Dad.
No, no... no...
We... we need to call the cops!
We need to call the cops, please.
- You don't have to...
- Hey!
You shouldn't have come to India.
But you did!
You have no idea
what is happening here.
No need to understand also
and we don't have time for that.
In this situation
there's only one person in
all of India
who can protect you.
Mother!
She doesn't easily trust
or accept any outsider.
You will have to convince her.
For whatever reason,
she should never get to know who you are.
Good evening, Teacher.
This is Diya from Vijayawada.
She knows our language.
A distant relative of our bank manager,
Mr Ajay Kumar.
She wants to teach English
to the kids in our school.
That post is vacant anyway.
Let's employ her.
She will stay in your guest house.
Uh... only if you agree.
What is your qualification?
Uh... English Literature.
Her AADHAAR Card...
Voter ID...
Class X, intermediate
and degree certificates...
I have verified them all, Teacher.
You can check them too.
Where did you work before this?
Siddhartha Convent.
Who is going to teach the kids? You?
Or she?
Where did you work before?
Siddhartha Convent.
Why did you quit?
Actually...
You are highly educated. Why
do you want to work in a place like this?
That's what I...
Mr Sarpanch,
I don't think she is up to the task.
Send her away and
find someone else.
When we reach a new place,
we like it
not because of that place.
It's because of the people there.
I have roamed several places
and finally come here.
Like how you are apprehensive
of trusting an outsider...
I am very apprehensive as well.
Let us both take a chance.
If it doesn't work out...
I will leave.
You can stay in the out house.
Not I, the children here
must like your teaching.
You have three days.
If the children don't like you,
you must leave on the fourth day.
Hey, get up!
If you don't bring your parents tomorrow,
or don't turn up at school,
you will know who I am.
Leave!
Why did you lie?
Who lied?
Hey, get going.
Children are like molten iron.
If we mold them well,
they become lamps that spread light.
If we don't,
they become blood-shedding...
...weapons.
Get freshened up and come.
I will get you some food.
I did as you instructed.
She has agreed.
Please let me go.
Hey, Sarpanch!
-Jessy?
-Sir, that girl is missing.
She hasn't been eating
since yesterday, Madam.
He should be killed.
For the past seven years
you have been sitting
like this in darkness,
on the bare floor,
in the burning smoke.
I know for a fact that no hunger matches
the hunger for vengeance.
Krishnakanth couldn't be traced.
Even though his daughter came here,
our men failed to catch her.
But no matter where she is, I'll find her
and make her kneel in front of you.
Even to exact your revenge,
you need to stay alive.
Our time has come.
More than finding her, their plan
would be to make sure
she doesn't leave India.
File a case against the girl.
- It won't happen again.
- Case?
-Charge her with murder.
-Murder?
-Whose murder should I mention?
-Please, sir!
Do your job.
They will file a case against her and
inform the Embassy and police stations.
You got to take a look at this.
Aadhya Krishnakanth, 28 years old...
US National, murdered Jessy Bhagga.
Varanasi outskirts.
-Hey...
-Brother?
Send our men in all directions.
Bus stations, railway stations, ports,
airports, highways, borders...
Their men will be everywhere.
-There should not be any mistake.
-Okay, boss.
They can come here any time.
They are searching for this car.
Dismantle it immediately.
Could you find where the vehicle
with that girl went?
Found it on a CCTV footage, sir.
They left that van at a warehouse
and went out in a black SUV.
Obulamma has already
instructed Hazare to find that girl.
Why are we also searching for her?
We are not looking for the girl.
We are looking for Krishnakanth.
For the past seven years,
we have been searching for him.
We searched every nook
and corner of the country.
We have access to every single
CCTV camera in the country.
But not a single CCTV could capture him.
We don't know where he is.
Then what is the relation
between the girl and him?
There is a relation!
Wherever she is...
he is bound to be there.
Find that vehicle first.
Hello!
Can anybody hear me?
-Good morning, Teacher.
Ma'am.
Though we locked her in,
the English teacher came out.
Someone locked the door from outside.
-That's why I am late...
-Chandru.
Yes, Ma'am.
Take this teacher to her classroom
and explain the syllabus to her.
-Let's go.
-Good morning, Teacher.
Hitler has left.
Take the syllabus.
Take children. Take class.
And take care.
Okay, you all just look here.
Come on.
Hey, come here.
When the children have no interest,
why are you forcing them?
I won't send him to school from tomorrow.
Do whatever you want.
I will burn you all to ashes.
What you did is a mistake. Do you
want them to become like you?
Hey! All of you are
attending school from tomorrow.
Understand?
She sounds crazy, doesn't she?
Even I used to think
about her the same way.
Most of those who live here
work in that coal mine.
Even small children work there
for daily wages.
Four years ago, Teacher
came to this place.
She literally begged everyone
and got this school reopened.
Since then, she has been educating
the children in this school.
Now let's meet another person.
Though Teacher is like this,
her son is entirely different.
Hey, you! Are you blind?
Can't you see?
But it was your mistake.
No problem, Uncle.
Sorry, brother.
I will move back.
Though he looks tall and imposing,
he doesn't even retaliate
when someone behaves rudely with him.
He doesn't mingle with anyone
or talk to anyone.
Neither does he get angry
despite eating so much chilli.
But when he is with kids...
he becomes one of them.
What is this suspense?
Should we wait for you so long
every single day?
Hey, like a batsman sent to bowl,
they gave me all sorts of assembling work.
Had they asked me
to disassemble something...
I would've done it in a single strike.
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
Sixer!
Salute!
He hit a sixer against your bowling
and you are saluting him?
You are always playing with us.
Don't you have friends of your own?
Hey, pass me the ball.
How many times should I tell you?
You should be home by 6 in the evening.
I told you once and isn't that enough?
Do I need to tell you this every day?
If you repeat this...
I won't be late from tomorrow, Mom.
Excuse me.
Bilal said I can leave today.
Just one more day.
Should eliminate!
Stop! Enough!
Stop... Just stop it!
Nobody can teach any of you.
Why?
Why are you doing this to me?
Very bad.
It's impossible to teach you.
So bad!
-Good morning, Teacher.
Please, sit down.
Your teacher seems tired.
She cannot teach today.
She will go to the market
and buy lights.
One run.
Where is the ball?
Look there.
Hey!
When did you start
playing cricket without me?
Why don't you come to play?
I will come tomorrow. Go.
Hey, let's go. Got the ball!
You asked me to tell you if she goes out.
Hitler has sent the English teacher
to the market.
Hello, hello! Madam!
You brought everything for double
the price and where are you going?
You are my property.
I am your owner.
Hey, you got a nice property, man.
Hey, leave her alone.
Hey! The hero is here.
He is going to beat us all
and take her away.
Come on.
Hit me, come on, hit me.
Hit me!
Hey, hit me!
My face is broken.
He thinks that he is a great hero.
Hey, it's the cops!
Let's go.
The vehicle was last seen
near Navada toll in Bihar.
We don't know where
it went from there.
Where could it have gone?
Send her photo to all our men.
I will send it immediately, sir.
What is taking Hazare so long?
Is he not capable of nabbing
even a girl?
Madam, it's Nayak!
What is it, Nayak?
Obulamma...
The consignment you were asking
about has arrived at Kandla Port.
Tell me when the delivery should be made.
Didn't I ask you to deliver it to Nepal?
Don't call me again.
Whatever comes up,
Vedha will take care of it.
That's it?
Only these many?
They didn't even bring weapons with them.
That one man is enough.
Hey, Nayak!
How are you?
It's a hundred million dollar consignment.
A small one.
But if you deliver this properly,
you will get many more big deals.
You are the right guy for this job.
Nepal!
Fine.
Then I will go and roam around Nepal.
He doesn't even look interested.
Hey.
Don't disturb me until we reach Nepal.
Don't worry.
No one will stop the consignment
once he stamps that seal on it.
Will he even be able
to get out of the port?
This is how you flush
a hundred million dollars down the toilet!
Sir!
The cops have surrounded us!
Open it!
Hey, close the door!
Close the door!
Hey, open the gate.
Open it!
What is it?
Nothing, sir.
We got information about this
cocaine consignment one month ago.
Why did we let them go, sir?
Did you see the seal?
Do you know where it came from?
Before you could think of even saying
the name of the place, they will kill you.
The seal?
Who stopped it?
Call all the control rooms and tell them
that nobody should stop the seal.
What are you saying, sir?
The seal?
I shall inform right away.
Inform everywhere immediately.
Yes, sir.
I have heard about that place as a child.
That some tribes rule the place.
That they have built huge
walls barring outsiders
and they have a strong army
and the most advanced weapons.
But isn't that an urban legend?
I don't know if that place exists or not
but it true that I got scared
when I heard about it.
I told you.
There is nobody in India
who can stop that seal.
Cutout...
Hey, I am painting. Be careful.
Hey! Stop that.
It's my birthday today. Go!
Don't you know that you must
wish me exactly at midnight?
Sorry, Pari. I forgot about it.
Happy birthday.
Okay, fine. Come.
Let's cut the cake.
Come on!
-Let's cut the cake.
-It's your birthday. You should cut it.
No, you should cut the cake.
-Hey, come on.
-No. It's your birthday...
Hey, come on.
I am getting angry.
-Come on, come.
-Hey!
Hey! Move out, quick!
Hey!
That thing...
Give it to me.
Just a small knife!
That too a plastic knife.
Vijay...
Yes, Teacher?
You remember the song I taught you?
Yes, Teacher.
Sing it.
In every story it's the demon
Who unleashes violence
And to oppress that demon
Rises a king...
In his quest to quell the enemy
The king has embraced savagery
He has made violence
A habit and forgotten how to smile
He slayed the monster,
Fighting resolutely
Filled with ire, he has turned into
A monster himself
If one has your courage
he will definitely succeed
Remember, oh skilled warrior,
Forgive and live on this land
Enough of anger
Now sing a song of love
Stop a war with a smile
And no more war and pain
Climb up that rock
with the truth
Your name is etched
all over that rock
Whatever written over it
Was erased in heavy rain
Chandru, Chandru!
Where did he go?
He has to take
lunchbox to the coal mine.
I shall take it.
Let me be useful at least for this.
This girl?
Sir, this girl is right here.
She is here in Tinsukia.
-What happened?
-We found the girl.
She is in Tinsukia, Assam.
Tinsukia?
It is near the borders of Burma.
There is a coal mine on the outskirts.
Majority of the people working
there have migrated from our place.
Are there any CCTVs there?
It's a very remote place, sir.
They don't even have
banks or post offices.
Then...
They must be there.
-Sir?
-Leave for Tinsukia immediately.
Come on, guys.
Who are you sending there?
I'm sending Selfie.
Sir.
Keep sending photographs from Tinsukia.
Okay, sir.
Let's go.
Oh, no! This girl is good for nothing.
Actually, I was...
I know.
There is only one more day, right?
-Hey, baby...
-Hey!
Smile!
Wow! Amazing!
Come. Let's go.
Hey!
Help!
Is he her savior?
She must have mistaken him
for someone else.
He is not capable of doing that.
My goodness! I don't know from
where the Sarpanch got this girl.
She is absolutely good for nothing.
She took one box and forgot the other.
She never does anything right.
Where is she?
Hey, hey!
Where are you dragging her?
Let her go!
I'm talking to you.
Why are you guys not helping?
Go, save the girl.
There are so many men here!
Can't any of you save her?
Oh, no! Look, can no one save her?
Oh, no! Anyone?
Please, someone help her!
No one will stop them and no one can.
There is only one person
who can stop them.
And that's you.
Oh, no! So many...
There are so many men out here.
Is no one capable?
Your son is here as well, right?
Why don't you ask him? Isn't he a man?
Oh, damn!
We have left him behind.
Cut his head off and bring it to me.
The ash formed on the burning coal
needs to be blown away
so that the heat inside can be felt.
Hey, they are going to kill our cutout.
What can the poor guy do?
He is like an old rusty
vehicle that would never start.
It was me who bound you
not to raise your hands on anyone.
Now, I set you free
from any bounds whatsoever.
Deva!
Stop them!
You can even plead with them.
Or make them bleed.
Just one strike!
Now your face is broken.
Go upstairs and pack everything.
You need to go today itself.
I am responsible for all of this.
I had convinced Deva
that she would be safe here.
I don't care about that.
Right now, all that matters to me
are my son and I, nothing else.
Neither do I have the leisure
to think about anyone else's problems.
Village after village, town after town,
city after city.
We were moving from one place to another.
I thought we would find peace here.
But now we have to get going again!
Where should I go from here?
Tell me, speak up.
Because of you, my son had to... again...
Take that girl and go away, Bilal.
This is my mother.
I came to India for this.
My mom always wanted to come to India.
But my dad would never allow her.
At least I have to fulfill
my mother's wish
of scattering her ashes here.
I know I have asked
you a lot, but...
Can you do this
one last thing for me? Please...
The children didn't like you, nor did I.
Take her away, Bilal.
Obulamma.
That girl...
They are not capable of it.
Hello.
There is a change
in the delivery point.
There is a check post near Budherabad,
under the control of the local Maoists.
They are our men.
Cross the check post and you
will reach the borders of Burma.
Deliver it there.
Along with that consignment,
you need to bring a girl as well.
Where is that girl now?
On the way to that check post, you
will find a small town named Tinsukia.
You should bring that girl from there.
It seems like we are lucky today.
Turn the vehicle.
The delivery point has been changed.
Let's go there.
Hey!
Let's go to the Burma border.
Come on, let's go.
Once you cross the border...
It's okay, Deva. I will take care.
Deva.
Let's get going.
Should eliminate!
Krishnakanth!
It's been so long since I saw you.
How are you?
It's me that you want, right?
I am here.
Kill me if you want
but please spare my daughter.
-Seal...
-Okay, sir!
Hey!
Stamp the seal on the girl
and then put her in the truck.
The girl must be already in the truck.
and been stamped with the seal.
They would be bringing her here.
You will be killed anyway.
You must watch your daughter
die with your own eyes.
She is not capable for this.
Find someone else.
Give me!
The children didn't like you, nor did I.
Once we reach Burma, we
won't be able to escape.
Answer some of my questions first.
Who are the people who want to kill me?
What did my dad do to them?
Why did they bring me to you?
Why did his mother react
so much, over a plastic knife?
Why doesn't he cross
the boundaries set by her?
And what is this?
Hold somewhere tightly.
What?
Obulamma.
If you know with whom
my daughter was all these days,
you will release her.
Hold there tightly.
He stopped.
He stopped the truck.
He stopped the truck?
Who the heck is he?
You should have killed him on the spot.
It's he.
Devaratha!
Nobody can stop him.
Hey.
You can stop a river with a dam, but
how can you stop a mighty ocean?
I never told this even you, Obulamma.
If I had, you would not have allowed me.
Thanks to your daughter, I found him.
Now he should be killed.
But no one can do anything to him.
That's why I put them
in that vehicle with seal
and made Devaratha
stop that truck.
The people who came to kill you...
Your father...
He, his mother...
Me...
And the seal. All have only
one thing in common.
Khansaar.
Don't you know what happens
if someone stops that seal?
Don't you know whose seal that is?
Someone has stopped the seal.
For the first time ever.
-And the one who stopped it is..
-I know.
Varadha...
Varadha Rajamannaar!
No one other than him can stop it.
Deva.
Khansaar changed
the fate of a lot of people.
But, what changed
the fate of Khansaar was
when two best friends
became arch-rivals.
My plan was amazing, wasn't it?
Now a war will happen
between the two of them.
And only one will survive.
You said no one can stop that seal!
The Salaar of Khansaar!
No one can stop that seal.
The Salaar to Varadha Rajamannaar.
But he is the one who created that seal!
Salaar Devaratha Raisaar!
What will happen now?
It's the rule he set.
Whoever breaks it must die!
Up... Up...
I am here for you.
That is the rule.
Some stories are frightening to listen to.
Some stories are frightening to watch.
Some stories are frightening
to even think of.
Do you want to listen to his story?
This story began a thousand years ago.
Dacoits more savage than Mahmud Ghazni
and Genghis Khan lived back then.
They would not just loot the villages
but would burn them to ashes.
They took all that they looted,
back to Khansaar.
Khansaar!
A forest situated between
mountains and the ocean.
There were three tribes
among those dacoits.
The Mannaar tribe.
The Shouryaanga tribe.
And the Ghaniyaar tribe.
The three tribes flourished and prospered
unchallenged for hundreds of years.
They turned that forest
into a formidable fortress.
Fire!
The British who could
reigned over the entire world
could occupy the whole of India but...
in Khansaar...
they couldn't even set foot.
Every time the British attempted to do
so, they ended up losing their own army.
After Independence, the newly
formed nation had a huge issue.
What should be done about Khansaar?
The then leader of the three
tribes, Shiva Mannaar went to Delhi.
He erased Khansaar from India's map.
He warned that the Constitution of India
won't be applicable to Khansaar
but every rule set by Khansaar
would be applicable to India.
Money generated through all
the illegal activities in India
like smuggling, gambling,
money laundering, drugs,
land petroleum, fake currency
and arms deal, were dealt by the agents
as per the percentage fixed by Khansaar.
To prevent the law and order
from interfering with their activity,
they began to dictate politics.
Fear...
Because of this weapon they had created,
no one dared to confront them.
People feared to even say
the name "Khansaar".
They turned this business
into a most profitable one
by investing in the emotion of fear.
Fully aware of the violent nature
of the tribes,
Shivmannaar decided bring Khansaar, which
was progressing to affluence,
under a common law.
Drafting a set of rules to be
strictly adhered to by everyone,
and named that book "Constitution".
And according to Constitution
he divided Khansaar into 101 parts
and appointed leaders for each part.
He crafted a bracelet
as a symbol of their authority.
He then divided the leaders
into three major groups.
He named sixty-one leaders with only
one vote each as "Governors"
and eight leaders with at least
three votes each as "Lords".
And with 15 votes for himself,
Shivmannaar pronounced himself
as the King of Khansaar.
One day, Shivmannaar died.
As per the agreement between
the three tribes,
after Shivmannaar's death,
Dhaara, leader of Shouryaanga tribe,
was supposed to become the king.
But, Rajamannaar did not to give
his father's throne to anyone else.
How dare they want to have my throne!
Not a single soul from
Shouryaanga tribe should be spared.
Can we confront them?
There is only one way to eliminate them.
Men, women, elderly and children...
Kill all of them while
they are asleep.
If even one life is spared,
the Shouryaangas' vengeance
will be unimaginable.
Why are you...
Thus, the Shouryaanga tribe
was completely eliminated.
Fearing another massacre,
everyone else bowed to Rajamannar.
He built a huge fort around Khansaar,
deployed a strong army,
and made Khansaar
a formidable force.
Rajamannaar, along with 61 Governors,
gave five out of eight Lord positions
to the Ghaniyaar tribe.
Vaali.
Gurung.
Cheeka.
Ranga.
And Naarang.
He gave the remaining three
Lord positions to his family members.
Om, Rajamannaar's
first wife's elder brother.
Bhaarava, Rajamannaar's son-in-law.
Rudra, Rajamannaar's son
by his first wife.
Radha Rama.
Rajamannaar's daughter
by his first wife.
Rajamannaar's honor and pride.
Though there were a lot of differences
among the Lords and Governors
nobody dared to go
against Rajamannaar's will.
These people, who were synonymous
for violence for over a 1,000 years
lived a peaceful life for 25 years
until that day.
Father, is it true?
Are you going out of Khansaar?
I will go instead, if necessary.
Temples were built to propagate religion.
Kingdoms are ruled to propagate legacy.
Khansaar is built
to propagate only one thing...
Fear.
I have maintained it until now.
No one should cross that line of fear.
Who is crossing that line now?
I am going out
of Khansaar to find that out.
Rama, until I come back, I am
leaving Khansaar under your watch.
And I am sure that
you will take care of it well.
Okay, Father.
My King.
I know that nobody will
disobey your decisions.
But, as your son-in-law,
I would like to ask you something.
Can't you forgive him at least now?
-Whom?
-Your son.
Varadha.
Did you give up your bracelet so easily?
Why did you do that?
He threw away the honor I gave him.
He lost his right to be my son.
But, he was just a ten-year-old.
Why are you justifying him?
Because no one else has the courage
to stand in front of you and say this.
Because, even now, you leave a chair
vacant for Varadha on your dining table.
Whenever I see your father Shivmannaar,
he reminds me of
Varadha... because of that!
He is also your blood, my King.
He also deserves the authority
which Rudra has got.
For the past 30 years,
I have been sitting on this throne
and taking decisions only for Khansaar.
For the first time,
I am making a decision for myself.
All I want is one of your chairs.
You are the only one who would give me
anything I ask for,
without any conditions.
Hence, I am asking you...
Ranga!
I wish to see my son, Varadha Rajamannaar,
as a Lord while I am still alive.
Varadha...
The son of Rajamannaar's second wife.
As he had given up his bracelet
when he was a child,
he couldn't become a Lord.
Though he was demoted as a Governor,
he always lived
with the confidence of a Lord.
Will you give it to me, Ranga?
You shouldn't request, my King.
You should only command.
I am going out of Khansaar
on a very important errand.
Once I come back, all the formalities
for making Varadha Rajamannaar a Lord
should be done by you, Bali.
Yes, my King!
Do you know why he asked
for your chair out of all of us, Ranga?
I am sure you know it.
Your father picked up the bracelet
he threw on the ground
and became a Lord
He did not earn it. It was thrown at him
like a piece of bone to a stray dog.
But my dad had genuinely won that day!
Had he asked for my life,
I would have willingly given.
How can I give away my chair?
Give it up.
Will you give it up...
Ranga?
King Rajamannaar's orders
cannot be defied.
There is another order
more powerful than Rajamannaar's orders.
Khansaar Constitution.
And in that book, there
is a very important rule.
"The strongest shall prevail.
"The strongest shall...
rule."
Ranga, yours is a new vengeance.
But Rudra's vengeance started
from the time Varadha was born.
You might be wondering why I'm showing
so much concern for you.
Today he asked you to give away
your chair.
Tomorrow it could be my turn.
But that is not what
the Constitution says.
I may beat you.
Then you beat me.
Let us fight.
The strongest shall have the country.
The strongest shall have
the chair.
Is Rudra off to kill Varadha?
I can't believe this.
Rudra has sent for Pandit.
Pandit?
When Rajamannaar returns
Varadha will be made a Lord.
Our Brother is a Lord now!
But by the time Rajamannaar returns,
what if Varadha is not alive?
The strongest shall have the country.
The strongest shall have the chair.
Ranga...
You want to slit his throat.
But I want the Mannaar authority
that he has.
The Constitution!
Rudra, it's the Constitution!
No one should disobey it.
Who? Who stopped me?
Who stopped me?
Hey!
At the court of our King Rajamannaar,
in his presence or absence,
no one shall raise
their voice or run their mouth.
It was me who stopped you.
How can you to take that decision?
Because I am representing the King now,
and that's why all of you are still alive.
If it was the King,
all of you would have been
beheaded by now.
Bali!
Madam!
In order to stop any sort of violence
between the Lords and
the Governors of Khansaar,
I am imposing a ceasefire.
On the orders of the acting King,
a ceasefire is imposed
in Khansaar from today!
The Constitution.
All stand equal before
the Khansaar Constitution.
The book has given all of us
the authority to defy
even our king at any circumstances.
I, Rudra Rajamannaar,
in the rank of a Lord, propose
a voting to lift the imposed ceasefire!
As per the Khansaar Constitution,
after nine days, a voting will be
held in Kotagada to decide
whether the ceasefire should be
withdrawn or sustained.
No one waited
until the voting day.
Right from the Lords to the Governors,
everyone began to deploy
the most merciless and powerful armies.
Rudra brought Pandit along.
Naarang assembled Russian soldiers.
Gurung assembled the Serbians.
Even the Governors
gathered at least 50 suicide killers.
Today, there were about
700 new entries at the gate.
Not sure how many more armies
might enter Khansaar.
Do you know how intimidating
each one of them are?
And the kind of weapons
they carry...
You tell me.
Which army are we bringing?
Tell me.
Where is our army?
Brother, tell me please.
We also set out to bring an army.
In just one jeep and
with only one vacant seat.
Even I was curious to see the army
that was supposed to fit in that seat.
Hey, Deva!
Varadha, my dad will skin me alive
if I go out now.
I am not coming.
You can leave.
-Hey...
-I said I can't.
Deva...
Do you remember me?
Only your voice has changed.
Not the way you call me.
Other than my mother,
only one person calls me Deva.
Varadha Rajamannaar.
How are you, mother?
I am starving.
Cook something for me.
It's been so long since I ate your food.
Hey...
I told you to leave.
Why are you still here?
Hey... Where is your nose ring?
It's... You...
Who took it?
Let me tell my mother. I will come.
Varadha wanted
to take Deva with him at any cost.
But Deva's mother had
decided not to send him along.
Mother!
-I think Varadha needs me...
-But...
Go with him...
Let's go get it.
-Sir...
-Need to make an entry.
-Rani... Rani...
-Surabhi!
Don't cry! Don't cry, dear!
Please, let her go.
She will never come back.
How many persons, sir?
Only one.
Isn't there anyone else, sir?
I won't need anyone else.
Surabhi!
What is his name?
Devaratha.
Which tribe?
He is an outsider.
Take his prints.
I am praying to our Goddess to save us.
Dear, no matter how much we pray,
no God would set foot on this sinful land.
How many times should I tell you?
He got scared just by looking
at the entrance gate.
Be careful, sir.
Whoever steps inside
never comes out.
Dear, whom are you praying to?
Huge walls are built out of fear.
Not out of fear of those going out...
You said God won't come to save us.
So, I am praying
in the opposite direction.
...but out of fear of those coming in.
Let's see if at least the demon
comes to our rescue.
After 25 years, in order to
keep the promise he had made...
he came back
to the land of his birth.
-Baba, this is...
-I know.
Don't look around.
No one else will be coming.
Of course, I know.
Varadha has made an entry
in the register for his army at the gates.
Only one entry must
has been made at the gate.
Only one?
You brought only one man?
We needed a whole army,
and you brought just one?
-Him, of all people?
-I forgot to ask.
Did you make all the arrangements
for Deva's stay here?
Yes, I did.
Have you forgotten?
It's because of that one decision
you made for him 25 years ago
our lives are so miserable even today.
And yet you have brought him back.
-Have food.
-You be quiet, Baba.
-Even now he could...
-Rinda!
Tell Satthi that the curry
is not spicy enough.
Deva won't like it.
Tell him to add some chilli
before you serve him.
Everyone in Khansaar
desperately wants to hack us to pieces.
Do you know that?
Father, why are you in a hurry
to take such a decision?
I want you to sit on that chair
while I am still alive
and fulfill my wish
of seeing you as a Lord.
-But, Dad...
-Hey...
Until now, I have fulfilled all
your wishes even before you asked.
Just fulfill this one wish of mine.
Vishnu!
Rudra Mannaar has sent you a message.
Lord Rudra?
I will do anything for him. What is it?
He asked you to give Varadha
sleepless nights.
Baba, we are going out.
Please call Deva as well...
There's so many of us. Why do we need him?
Hey... Come.
Go, get him.
I will hit you!
Go!
Lord!
Why are you walking, my Lord?
Hey, hold an umbrella for him.
Where is the umbrella?
I know our present condition very well.
I also know that we have
only enemies around us.
Hey...
What is it?
More than the fear of getting killed,
I dread the humiliation
that we are yet to suffer.
Who is that?
All of them are desperately
waiting to chop your head off.
I feel like chopping off your head
right now, right here.
If we want to stay alive here...
however large an army we get,
it won't be enough.
In Khansaar, nothing can be
calculated using a calculator.
That's why I brought a maniac
who is totally unpredictable.
But, what is he going to do?
Hold the gun tight.
Keep your body upright
while pulling the trigger.
Safety...
you can fire after unlocking
the safety lock.
A mechanic only knows how to use
a spanner and a wrench.
What is the use of giving him a gun?
That's it, right?
Let's go.
Why are you here, my Lord?
Hey, I don't see any vacant tables?
I will get the tables ready
at once, my Lord.
At times, I feel it's better
that he doesn't do anything.
Fold your hands, all of you!
Don't you know the procedure?
Mother...
Where are you going?
We have some other work, let's go.
-Hey, there...
-Come on, come...
Ganga...
Rudra on one hand and Ranga on the other.
Now, my son Vishnu
as well is troubling you.
It's sad to see Rajamannaar's son
going through all these.
Do one thing.
Chop your head off
and place it at my feet.
It's my mistake.
I didn't notice.
How long would you tolerate this?
Even I don't know how long
I can hold him back.
Hey, leave me.
Khansaar's king,
Rajamannaar's son...
Varadha Rajamannaar!
See my plight now!
I have absolutely no value here.
What are you saying?
-Baba.
-Didn't you hear that?
Deva! Please sit down... please...
None of my people are happy
that I brought you here.
They are just not saying it out loud.
But I'm sure they are cursing me.
Nobody even bothered to
ask me why I brought you here.
-You won't ask me.
-Brother, you've had enough.
Let's go.
Hey... come here, my dearest brother...
Brother! Let me go, brother.
Hey, you guys bring him home.
Baachi!
I am really scared, my friend.
Not that something will happen to me.
Not that the little honor
I have left will be taken away.
I am only worried
about my younger brother.
You must make sure
nothing happens to him.
Hey...
You must look after him.
You must take care of him...
Move your hand.
You must take care of him.
When I am gone...
he...
Deva!
You have six hands and yet...
Not one is extended to help
We are in deep anguish
And you are nowhere to be seen
Why do you harbor anger
Against the fragile
To hail you with raised arms
There is no strength left
Even with ceaseless worship,
We remain untouched by mercy
We called you again and again
Yet hope has faded away
Along with Rudra, Ranga and Bhaarava,
another ten Governors have teamed up.
They will try to influence
the others to take their side.
Rudra, whatever you say,
we won't go against our King.
Good.
When I become the king, I will
tell everyone around me
that there lived a very
loyal man like you.
But, my Lord...
You cannot win without the Ghaniyaars.
And no Ghaniyaar
will go against Naarang.
Naarang!
What if Ranga tries to influence
some of the Ghaniyaars?
If any one of us goes against our king,
I will kill him
with my own hands, my Lord.
-Do you have children?
-What?
Children.
Boy.
Girl?
Girl...
Hey, Pandit!
He is wearing the bracelet.
Not now.
Just be patient for four more days.
Girl.
I also have a wish.
What is it, Naarang?
A wish to be a father
like our King Rajamannaar.
They are here again!
Mother...
After the ceasefire voting
I wish to see my son in my chair.
As soon as the ceasefire voting gets
over, your son will become a Lord, Uncle.
Brother, Vishnu asked us
to go to Mahara.
This bloody...
-Hey!
-Sir?
Under no circumstances should
Deva know where we are going.
Even if he comes,
what can he do?
Hey, tell him.
Deva shouldn't come there.
Hey, where is Devaratha?
Damn! How can I make him
understand?
Where is he?
It's useless to ask him.
Vishnu had a procedure there.
First, he flies the kite high.
Hey, stop right there.
Then he cuts the string himself.
Whichever house
the kite lands on...
He takes one girl from that house.
Oh, God! No!
Oh, no!
Oh, yeah... we got our chick.
No... I'll go.
You must take care
of our mother and Surabhi.
You are so young.
I am the elder one.
Listen to me.
This is on me.
No, no. I will go.
Oh, no!
It doesn't matter if you go or she.
It doesn't matter who goes.
It's the same for me.
O Goddess! Save us, please!
Oh, no!
Surabhi!
I don't know which girl is coming.
I cannot bear the suspense.
-Surabhi...
-What are you doing?
-Surabhi... Surabhi...
-Don't go!
Hey, who called him here?
Hey!
Follow the procedure.
Stand with your hands folded.
Good.
Sir! Please spare her!
-Be quiet!
-Sir, sir...
Look at me!
She is just a kid.
Where did you all go today,
leaving me behind?
That territory is called Mahara.
I beg you, my Lord. Leave her.
It's like a poultry farm.
That scoundrel Vishnu
chooses a hen every day
and kills it.
Please spare her, sir!
Let's take her home.
Hey, I don't have the patience.
Leave her alone.
Give us two minutes, dear Lord.
I will get her ready like a lady.
-But, instead of the hens, it's...
-Baba.
We have other important things to do.
Let's go.
O Goddess Kaliyamma!
Your rituals are wrong.
If you want to please the Goddess...
go to the animal market first.
From the herd, select a nice and
healthy ram with strong twisted horns.
Hey, stop it!
Dear Lord!
Hold it by the horns and drag it down.
Garland it, apply turmeric
and vermilion on its face.
Then, sharpen the knife.
Hey, I am warning you!
I won't tell you again.
Sprinkle holy water on its face.
Mutthu!
As soon as it shakes its head...
Shall I complete the ritual now?
Hey, kill him!
Hey!
Look at what he is doing, Brother!
Come on, fast!
Go!
Surabhi!
Goddess Kaliyamma didn't come.
Instead...
she has sent her son for us.
Brother, he will kill Vishnu.
If he dies, you know
what our plight will be, right?
Varadha! Stop him right now!
I know him since childhood.
He won't stop.
Until he stops breathing...
Are you going to kill me?
Do you know who my father is?
Baba!
Stop him, Baba.
I will kill you!
Kill that scoundrel!
Just two minutes...
I will get him ready like a Lord.
Hey!
I am just checking
if you are real or not, son.
Vishnu has been killed.
Was it him?
Why did Deva react so violently
for that poor girl he didn't even know?
I don't understand it even today.
I understand!
In every girl who is in distress,
he sees his mother.
How dare he touch the child!
That too a girl child!
Sorry.
What he did that day
affected not only me
but the entire Khansaar.
This shouldn't be happening.
Especially during the ceasefire.
This is going to impact
the upcoming voting.
Ceasefire was enforced to stop
Varadha from getting killed.
How could he go and do this?
Varadha didn't kill him.
The new guy did.
What do we do?
Now he is under the control
of the Mannar army.
But we cannot take
any decision about this right now.
The decision will be made
by Naarang at Velamgadi.
He will surely not spare Varadha.
Rudra!
I heard that Varadha would be
handed over to Naarang at Velamgadi.
Is he going to kill him?
But it's my prerogative to kill him.
Since it was the new guy
who flouted the rules,
you must convince Naarang
to punish the culprit.
If Varadha dies, I will be happy.
But I must follow my dad,
the King's command.
Uncle, I will speak to Naarang.
Please go to Varadha.
Rudra...
I haven't asked you
for anything since childhood.
Do something, please.
I want Varadha.
Tomorrow at Velamgadi...
Naarang is going to pronounce the verdict.
All arrangements have been made.
What does it mean?
If you want to come out,
don't open your mouth there.
What does it mean?
I know this is not
the right time to say this.
You have all the rights to do whatever
you want with the one who killed your son.
Varadha didn't kill your son.
The one who killed him is the new guy.
Remember that!
My Lord...
If the ceasefire has to be lifted,
Varadha must be killed.
It's true that Varadha
didn't kill your son.
But...
when your son Vishnu
was mercilessly murdered
he stood there without doing anything.
The verdict at Velamgadi today
has nothing to do with Kotagada.
Whatever happens there, no one
should lift a finger.
All of you remove cartridges
from guns.
Until I say, nobody should use weapons.
Somebody's head will roll today.
As soon as it happens,
inform me.
I will take care of everything there.
You just need to remain silent.
Understand?
Isn't he the one who killed Vishnu?
I heard he killed as many as 25.
Will he chop his head
or Varadha's head today?
He is drawing sword!
He is going towards Varadha, bro!
Hey!
He is going to kill your rooster.
Deva...
Deva!
It was me who killed your son.
Do whatever you want with me.
Don't touch Varadha.
-Varadha is innocent.
-Deva, wait.
You can punish me.
Give me any punishment.
I..
I am begging you.
Please spare Varadha.
Deva!
Deva! Listen to me.
Stop right there.
I am the one
who killed your son Vishnu.
Hey...
Kill me.
But...
Please don't touch Varadha.
Hey, bring him aside.
Hey, move aside.
Sir...
He didn't do anything.
It was for me.
Kill me, sir.
I told you to spare Varadha!
Didn't I tell you not to touch my Varadha?
What are you looking at?
Finish then off!
Load your guns!
No one should touch him.
Please!
I...
kindly..
..request!
Is it Varadha's head?
Or the new guy's?
The new guy decapitated Naarang, Rudra.
You muted me in Khansaar.
But he decapitated
two people at high volume.
Maybe he doesn't know the rules...
What if he knows them
but didn't follow them?
Of course!
Varadha said it correctly...
Seriously, he got himself a maniac.
Before Devaratha came
here, we were on a frying pan,
getting our lives fried
and burnt.
He killed his son
and threw us into the fire.
I wish they spare at least our bones.
But no.
He has killed his son.
Ask me where he is going to
send us from this fire.
That's a suspense.
What?
Brother... brother... brother...
You gave him a pet name when he was young.
What was that?
I forgot! I forgot! I forgot!
Can you remind me?
You gave him a name with a lot of pride!
What was it? Tell me.
Tell me, brother. Tell me, tell me...
Tell me!
Hey!
Hey, brother! Hey, brother! Tell me!
-Hey...
-Hey, sit down!
I warned him not to touch you.
Didn't I?
You heard me, right?
How could he touch you!
No one should touch you!
Sorry.
I should be saying sorry.
It was all my fault.
No matter what happened here,
many times I stopped myself
from getting you involved in all these.
But I couldn't anymore.
I knew this is how it would end
once you come here.
You would have done great
anywhere but here.
Despite knowing that...
Sorry.
What could be more important
to dad than this?
He doesn't answer my calls at all.
Uncle, did you hear anything
about him?
If he doesn't turn up,
we will lose for sure.
There are 101 votes in total.
Since Naarang and Vishnu are dead,
they will invalidate their four votes.
97 votes remain.
With nine votes of Bhaarava,
Ranga and you, our votes would be 24.
We cannot trust the remaining voters.
Zorani, Acharya, Mishra,
Akram Pasha, Shukla...
I will bring all of them here.
You must hand over Varadha
to me after voting.
What are you going to do with him?
What is our vote count
including all of them?
Including the King...
Forty eight.
I will show you
what I am going to do with Varadha.
I will give drugs to all prisoners
and turn them into beasts.
Upon seeing red,
they would become violent.
Do you know what they would do then?
Hey, get up!
I will send a hundred such men
to Varadha.
Let's assume that the King would be back.
We need Varadha's vote also.
Right from childhood I know
that you are my father's blood.
I have despised you ever since.
If these bars were not here,
you would have known
how deeply I hate you.
King Rajamannaar won't turn up
for the voting tomorrow.
Everything will go as I expected.
Take this as an advice or a warning.
If you vote to lift the ceasefire
I will kill you!
A man goes to any extent
to achieve something he loves.
But to destroy something he hates...
he goes even beyond that.
I hated you even before
my younger brother did.
King Rajamannaar is coming
to Kotagada tomorrow.
If you vote for lifting the ceasefire
and disrespect him,
I will definitely divert all my hatred
towards the one you love the most.
Badri!
Madam!
If things don't go as I say tomorrow,
drag his brother out and behead him
once the voting is over.
If it's my father's blood that
runs through your veins,
you will make the right decision.
Bhaarava, I am very scared.
Do you think today's voting
will go as we expect?
It has to.
And it will!
Finally, it's our time.
Hear... hear... hear!
The voting process regarding
the ceasefire declared nine days ago
is about to begin at Kotagada today.
To make a decision on this, first
the Governors, followed by the Lords,
and finally the King
shall use their voting right.
Those who want the ceasefire to end
shall place their bracelets
on the left plate of the scale.
Those who want the ceasefire to continue
shall place their bracelets on
the right plate of the scale.
As Varadha Rajamannaar is
an offender,
he can use his right to vote
only if there is a tie.
The voting shall begin now.
The voting should end before
the given time.
Governor number 1!
Governor number 10.
Governor number 41.
Governor number 6!
Governor number 26. 37.
Governor number 32.
Four!
Governor number 14!
5!
Governor number 2! 60!
Governor number 50! 3!
Governor 22!
I checked flight arrivals to Khansaar.
There is no information
about the King's arrival.
Now the Lords will cast their votes.
Only the King's fifteen votes are left.
If he doesn't turn up
before the time runs out,
the bracelets already used
for voting will be counted
and the verdict on
ceasefire will be announced.
Shivmannaar's son!
Khansaar's King, Rajamannaar
returns to his court!
Since it's a tie
with 48 votes on each side,
the verdict shall be based
on Varadha Rajamannaar's vote.
Make your disgrace complete now.
We don't know in whose favor
the voting will end.
But we can decide for which side
you are going to vote.
It doesn't matter what they think.
What decision are you
going to make?
Tell me.
For a hunter, the greatest pain
is not missing a prey,
but being not allowed to hunt.
Is allowing enough?
It's enough.
In that case,
declare the hunting season open!
I was waiting for you say it.
Khansaar must burn red!
Either with burning embers
or with their blood.
More than the redness of raging fire,
the crimson color of flowing blood
is always beautiful.
Thank you.
With your advice,
I have taken the right decision.
I too have...
the Mannaar blood
flowing through my veins.
Today, from 12:01 at night onwards,
based on the result of the votes,
the ceasefire has been lifted!
Now the rooster is yours.
They lifted the ceasefire?
Against them?
I mean how?
But the most important problem
was how to survive the night.
Oh, are you saying that your people
are in trouble because of us?
Varadha voted in their favor.
All must be chopped to pieces.
Get everyone out.
Finish off his younger brother first.
Sharpen the knife.
Come.
Do you like to watch tigers hunting?
I do not like it at all.
It's very boring.
I don't like it.
More than tigers, I like to watch
how wild dogs hunt.
It skins its prey
and eats the flesh
while it is still alive.
I wanted to kill you myself.
But I have no capacity for such violence.
That's why I have raised
some wild dogs.
I gave them all kinds of drugs
and made them rabid.
When they tear up your body,
and scatter the pieces.
I would relish that sight!
Now, we have a hope to live.
After a long time...
we have started worshiping again.
Don't be scared.
Nothing will happen to them.
Hey.
You won't even cut the skin
if you whet it like that.
Slant it and whet.
It must cut through his bones!
You want me to give you a tattoo now?
Can't you see death waiting
all around for you, sir?
Do you see it too?
What do you want me to tattoo?
Whatever you see in my eyes.
It's done, sir.
Where are they all going?
They must have found
something redder, sir.
Have you ever seen
the one who hunts the hunters?
You can see him now.
Your grim reaper is here.
You gave them drugs and made them mad.
But he was born mad.
Release the remaining dogs!
Why are you so late?
The tattoo took some time.
You are tired with so few men?
Hey, if I had a sword
I too would have performed
just like you did.
Here, take the bigger one.
Why didn't you come
back here for 25 years?
Why didn't you call me
I should have.
What happened?
Don't you know how to whistle?
Do you have admirers there?
Of course.
More than you.
But they are girlfriends.
I have some too.
But I got more applause than you.
The problems started when you
wanted to make Varadha a Lord.
We are all violent men.
Violence is in our blood.
I have been suppressing
that 1000-years-old violent nature
for the past 25 years.
I have a childhood story.
This was bound to happen some day.
The ceasefire was only an excuse
to fight amongst themselves.
I would stand on the terrace
every day looking at the entire Khansaar
and dream that one day
all this would be mine.
Enough fighting for bracelets
and breadcrumbs.
I want all that is
in front of my eyes.
Everyone is after my throne.
That is exactly why
they are joining hands.
The first to join hands
were our own people.
Did you think I would kill you, Uncle?
How can I kill my own blood?
If you and I stand together
we can bring every territory in Khansaar
under Mannaar rule.
What do you say, Uncle?
What makes you think
that uncle and Rudra have joined
hands against you?
Why do you think Rudra invited Pandit?
I know exactly what Pandit is capable of.
Secondly...
I went out of Khansaar because I
came to know about a huge weapons deal.
The order was placed from Khansaar.
Who?
Vaali.
Do you know why Rajamannaar
obliterated an entire tribe
but spared us, the Ghaniyaars?
Because we have no unity.
What happened to them should
never happen to us.
Khansaar is breaking
into pieces now.
If we stand united,
the whole of Khansaar will be ours.
Thiru...
Thirdly...
More terrible than these two.
The sin I committed 25 years ago
has come back to hunt me down.
Tell me.
Where are they?
Where is Bhaarava?
Bhaarava?
Your husband does not belong
to Mannaar tribe as you believe.
Then?
Do you know why I built
such huge walls around Khansaar?
Do you know why I hold the most powerful
weapons and maintain the biggest army?
Because I always have this fear
that at least one of them is still alive.
Who?
The Shouryaangas.
Bhaarava is a Shouryaanga?
Do you know how did we hid
our elderly, women
and children that day?
Wait, wait...
What?
Shouryaanga army was waiting
for the past 25 years,
all the while, causing internal conflicts
in Khansaar to weaken it.
We still feel the pain.
We have been living in hiding.
We have changed our names.
We have changed our identity.
All for this day.
When will you forgive him?
-Who?
-Your son.
If you don't eliminate
your enemies by tonight
The Constitution.
Naarang must defy Rajamannaar.
He must kill Varadha.
You beheaded our deity!
To burn you alive
along with your throne...
each one of the Shouryaangas
are eagerly waiting here.
Except one.
You...
remember Dhaara?
Our leader.
But you killed him.
But...
His son is still alive!
That night, your son Varadha rescued
Dhaara's son
and sent him out of Khansaar.
Leave immediately from here.
Did you just threw away your bracelet?
Why did you do that?
We have been looking
for him all these years.
But he has returned by himself.
Varadha has got
his army registered at the gate.
You all saw what he did
right after he set foot in Khansaar.
Vishnu was killed.
Was it him?
Our leader!
I will get our army ready, Father.
He is a...
Shouryaanga?
Wait, wait... wait...
I need a drink.
Do you have?
Inform our Mannaar army
to stay on high alert
not just at the Khansaar gates,
but throughout the city!
Whoa!
On one hand, all of Khansaar
is ready to go to war for the throne.
On the other, thousands of Shouryaangas
are ready
to burn the chair down.
But Deva had promised
the same throne to Varadha.
But...
The right to sit on that throne
belongs to...
Deva.
Does Deva know about this?
What if he finds out?
No one should survive.
You asked me about the name
I gave him as a child...
Salaar.